<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>notmyjunie</title>
	<subtitle>this is a test of some sorts</subtitle>
	<link href="https://notmyjunie.github.io/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://notmyjunie.github.io/"/>
	<updated>2024-03-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>https://notmyjunie.github.io/</id>
	<author>
		<name>notmyjunie</name>
		<email></email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>ThinkPad X1 Extreme, a week later</title>
		<link href="https://notmyjunie.github.io/blog/thinkpad-1week/"/>
		<updated>2024-03-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://notmyjunie.github.io/blog/thinkpad-1week/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;overview&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Overview &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://notmyjunie.github.io/blog/thinkpad-1week/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve spent a week with my Lenovo ThinkPad X1 Extreme Gen 1 and it has been a really neat laptop. For starters, the ThinkPad line of laptops from Lenovo (originally from IBM) are known to be good business laptops used in corporate/enterprise settings. They are most known for being absolutely rugged and tough to the core with easily replaceable parts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source type=&quot;image/avif&quot; srcset=&quot;https://notmyjunie.github.io/img/3GKBnGw9-7-350.avif 350w&quot;&gt;&lt;source type=&quot;image/webp&quot; srcset=&quot;https://notmyjunie.github.io/img/3GKBnGw9-7-350.webp 350w&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;ThinkPad X1 Extreme Gen 1&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; decoding=&quot;async&quot; src=&quot;https://notmyjunie.github.io/img/3GKBnGw9-7-350.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;350&quot; height=&quot;320&quot;&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;cost-and-reasoning&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Cost and Reasoning &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://notmyjunie.github.io/blog/thinkpad-1week/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I bought my ThinkPad X1 Extreme which is refurbished for about &lt;strong&gt;$600&lt;/strong&gt; which sounds alot when compared to the likes of a used T series laptop or even an older gen X1 Carbon. What must be considered when buying a used/refurbished ThinkPad is the selection of optional accessories included. Mine fortunately came with a fingerprint scanner and the ThinkShutter privacy feature for the webcam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason I chose this over the upgradeable T480 and the slim X1 Carbon is because of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://psref.lenovo.com/syspool/Sys/PDF/ThinkPad/ThinkPad_X1_Extreme/ThinkPad_X1_Extreme_Spec.PDF&quot;&gt;specs&lt;/a&gt; included. The ThinkPad X1 Extreme Gen 1 has a Kaby Lake Intel Core i7 included as its processor, which features an Intel UHD Graphics 630 as its internal GPU. Alongside an iGPU, this laptop also has an NVIDIA GeForce GTX1050 Ti (with Max-Q Design) as its dedicated GPU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My laptop was listed as 16GB RAM, however when I checked the specs of it once it arrived it turns out to have a 32GB RAM in it. I don&#39;t know whether this is on 1 RAM stick or 2 since I haven&#39;t open it up but, wow what a steal for this. There&#39;s also a 1TB SSD drive included.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Site Revamp</title>
		<link href="https://notmyjunie.github.io/blog/firstpost/"/>
		<updated>2024-03-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://notmyjunie.github.io/blog/firstpost/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have rewritten this site with the intent of making it compatible with md files for easier syntaxing. As of now, this site remains bare bones and not customised yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This website was built with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.11ty.dev&quot; title=&quot;Eleventy&quot;&gt;Eleventy&lt;/a&gt;, a really simple static site generator.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
